zumbox.com 2015-05-17

# Privacy | Digital Postal Mail

**Privacy Policy/Your California Privacy Rights**  
**For the Zumbox Website**  
**Last Updated: February 28, 2013**

 1\. **Our Commitment to Privacy**

1.1 Your privacy is of the utmost importance to Zumbox (“our”, “we”, and/or “us”). Because we collect certain types of information about the users of this Web site at www.zumbox.com (“ **Site** “) and its services, we feel you should fully understand the conditions of our collection and use of such information. This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** “) discloses what information we collect, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. By using this Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy.

1.2 This Privacy Policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect? What are the purposes for which we collect this information, and how is it used? How do we disclose information collected?
  * What security measures do we have in place to protect information we collect?
  * How do you correct and/or update the information we collect?
  * How do you “opt out” from allowing your information to be used by us for certain purposes?
  * What are cookies, and how do we use them?
  * What are my rights as a California resident?
  * How are you able to contact us?

1.3 If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with us, please contact us by email to [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com) using the subject title of “Privacy Policy”, by phone at 818-707-7400 (and mention that you have a Privacy Policy issue related to the Site) or by mail (either traditional or Zumbox) to 975 Business Center Circle, Thousand Oaks, CA 91320. Our Lead Customer Support Representative is our designated Privacy Policy consultant and monitors compliance with all international and domestic privacy regulations.

2\. **Information We Collect; How it is Used, and Purposes for Collecting Information**

2.1 We collect the following information from you: (a) information you explicitly provide to us by completing any submission, registration or account form(s) on or through this Site, including your name, email and street addresses, and, when applicable, credit card information, (b) information you send or receive via Zumbox mail, including the content, and (c) information that is automatically collected by us when you visit this Site (see Section 4 below). We use this information for our own internal purposes, which are more fully explained below. (Except in the case of content that is sent via Zumbox mail, with the intended recipient of such mail, unless it is necessary to do so in order to comply with state and federal laws, to verify your identity, to fulfill our obligations arising from this Site, or as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share this information with third parties, In some cases (as discussed below), we may share aggregated information with other parties.) For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “other parties” shall not include any affiliate of Zumbox (each, a “Zumbox Affiliate”), including, without limitation, its parent, subsidiaries, predecessors or successors in interest, assigns, any entity merged into or with Zumbox and its authorized representatives and consultants who assist in supporting the Site or any advertiser, municipality or other third party that distributes electronic content to you through your Zumbox mailbox (collectively, the “ **Subscribers** “) that is registered with Zumbox consistent with the Zumbox services you receive.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (defined herein as minors younger than thirteen years of age) in accordance with our Terms of Use.

2.2 If you subscribe to our email alerts, blogs or other public forums, we may ask for contact information (such as your name, email address and demographic information). We use this information in the same manner as we use your collected information during the account registration process and otherwise in this Site. Recipients of our email alerts and users of our blog can unsubscribe by following the instructions at the end of the email alerts or on this Site. We will, however, send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications if you want to receive Zumbox services as such communications are not promotional in nature. You may opt out of certain other communications, however, as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

3\. **Information Explicitly Provided by You; Creating a User Account and Authorization**

Visitors to this Site may create an account with us by completing and submitting a short registration form on this Site which requires them to fill out certain information about themselves. We use your personally identifiable information to contact you about the services on our Site in which you have expressed interest. Through the account creation process, we collect your contact information (like your telephone number and physical and/or e-mail addresses) and a user chosen password, and then conduct a verification process. By registering and providing information to us, you give us permission to confirm and verify your identity with third parties for the purpose of providing our services to you. The contact information we collect directly from you is used for our own internal tracking purposes, including, without limitation, identification, service selection and account evaluation, and in order to direct correspondence to you from third parties in connection with the services we provide to you, including, without limitation, mail delivered to your Zumbox mailbox from Subscribers. We also use this contact information from time to time to send you mail to your Zumbox mailbox, together with email alerts and other materials about Zumbox including information related to this Site and content updates. We also retain certain portions of your contact information for our internal records.

4.  **Information We Automatically Collect; IP Addresses**

When you connect to the Internet, your computer has a unique identification code called a “MAC ADDRESS”. You also have an “IP address”. Depending on the way you access the Internet, you may also have a different IP address each time you connect, or your IP address may be the same each time, or it may not be a unique IP address – you may share the IP address with others using your router. We log the IP addresses of users who visit this Site. We use your IP address for system administration purposes, such as to help diagnose problems with our server.

In connection with compliance with certain legal and regulatory requirements, we may use your IP address to help identify you. We may also use your IP address as a means to identify your location in order to better provide the Services, however we do not share specific information regarding an individual’s IP address with third parties.

5\. **Disclosure and Use of Collected Information**

5.1 **Generally.** We may provide aggregate information about visitors to this Site and our customers, sales, Site traffic patterns and related Site information to our Subscribers and affiliates, including, without limitation, our parent, subsidiaries, predecessors, successors and assigns or any entity merged into or with Zumbox.

5.2 **Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information.** We may disclose any and all information when legally compelled to do so. In other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires that we disclose your personally identifiable information or if disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site or any Zumbox Affiliate, we may disclose your personally identifiable information.

5.3 **Use of Information.** We use collected information for many purposes, including, but not limited to, providing you the services offered by Zumbox, administering and improving this Site, verification processing, diagnosing problems with our systems, developing new ideas and services, and communicating with you. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personally identifiable information (including any information gathered through the account registration process such as name and email address) with other third party companies for their commercial or marketing use. We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions and/or functionality on this Site.

We may use other third parties such as, as applicable, credit card processing companies to bill you for goods and services, email service providers to send out emails on our behalf, and a third party marketing provider to provide broadcast email services for us. When you sign up for the Zumbox services, we collect certain personally identifiable information such as your name, street address, and e-mail address that we may share with third parties of the type referenced above in order to best provide the services for which you have registered.

From time to time Zumbox may use third party data collection providers, like Wufoo, to gather data or survey information. The data is transmitted securely to Zumbox and as such, the third party does not retain the data. The collected data is used for the pre-qualification of subscribers’ service levels.

Although you may not “opt out” of the registration process if you wish to become a Zumbox member, you may choose to “opt out” or block senders of promotional materials from sending you mail through Zumbox and/or its affiliates, advertisers or other business partners. If you do not “opt out” or block senders of such promotional materials, Zumbox reserves the right to release any general demographic information regarding you to third parties who provide goods or services that we believe may be of interest to you, including, without limitation, to Subscribers. We will not release your credit card information to third parties unless necessary to complete a transaction between you and such a third party. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving promotional information from such third parties, including, without limitation, from Subscribers, please contact those third parties directly, or contact Zumbox at [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com).

Zumbox limits its own e-mail solicitations to those customers who have not “opted out” of receiving such communications. The solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail and provide the customer with a method of “opting out” of receiving future communications of a similar nature.

Finally, Zumbox may use individual members’ data to “pre-populate” forms which are displayed for the purpose of collecting individual data by Zumbox and/or its Subscribers. In no case does pre-populating a form automatically transfer any data to any advertiser or third party. Only if the member voluntarily requests that such data be transferred will any transfer take place, for example, if/when a member clicks a “submit form” button.

Keep in mind that, while Zumbox encourages all third parties involved including, but not limited to, its affiliates and Subscribers, to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and members and to otherwise handle personally identifiable information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from Zumbox or independently. Nevertheless, in the event that you encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association with, Zumbox that you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com); we will be happy to forward your message to the third party.

Except as noted above, Zumbox does not share, rent, or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties for their respective promotional purposes

6.  **Blogs**

If you use our blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit on those portions of the Site can be read, collected or used by other users of these forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Zumbox does not control the acts of its members or visitors and we are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@zumbox.com.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so.

7\. **Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. While Zumbox sends the invitation via email, the email appears to have been sent by you. Additionally, Zumbox does store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

8\. **Import Contacts**

Zumbox provides an address book feature that facilitates sending mail through Zumbox if you choose to use it by importing your contacts’ information via a CSV file (comma delimited); furthermore, each time you enter a new address as you send mail, these new addresses along with the entered addressee information – are automatically added to your address book. If you wish not to permanently retain an address, Zumbox provides the means to remove it as part of the address book functionality.

The Send Letter and the Send Postcard features collect additional information about third parties such as name and address. We use this information to facilitate sending mail, and not for any other purpose.

The information in your Zumbox address book is not used for any purposes outside of the intended feature of facilitating you sending mail.

9.  **Our Security Measures**

We take generally accepted industry security measures in order to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information we collect from you, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number, national ID) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt such information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you may contact our Lead Customer Service Representative to find out more about the security measures we have implemented.

10\. **How to Correct Your Information**

You have the ability to correct, delete or change any information and/or the address or other contact information which you have previously provided to us by accessing the “My Settings” area of zumbox.com or by sending an email to [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com) or by calling us at 818-707-7400 (and mention that you have an information correction issue related to the Site). You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at support@zumbox.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

11\. **How To Opt Out**

You have the opportunity to opt out of receiving further communications through our service from Zumbox or any Subscriber at any time after you have registered an account on this Site. You may do this in several ways. To opt out of receiving future emails or Zumbox mail from Zumbox, you may indicate your desire in the “My Settings” area of the Site. To opt out of receiving Zumbox mail from a specific Subscriber, you may “block” future mailings by selecting the “block” button in the “Mail” area of the Site. Alternatively, you may accomplish any of the above by sending an email to [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com) or by calling us at 818-707-7400 (and mention that you have an opt-out request related to the Site) and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within Zumbox’s database, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, Zumbox reserves the right, from time to time, to re-contact former customers or users of Zumbox’s services.

12\. **What Are Cookies and How Do We Use Cookies?**

12.1 “ **Cookies** ” are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s web browser on the user’s hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at this Site, and the websites visited just before and just after this Site. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from web page to web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus.

12.2 We use Site browser software tools such as cookies and web server logs to gather information about this Site’s users’ browsing activities in order to improve this Site and better serve users of this Site. This information helps us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve this Site to better meet the needs of our users and prospective users. We do not link cookies to personally identifiable information. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.

12.3 If you have turned off all cookies, many features of this Site will not be available to you.

13.  **Linked Websites and Advertisers**

13.1 This Site may contain links to other websites, as well as advertisements from companies with their own websites. We also allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within this Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on this Site. Such third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience segment (for example, women ages 18-25 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of this Site (but not any personally identifiable information), such as the number of times you viewed an ad, to determine which ads to deliver to you. The use of cookies by our advertisers, service providers, Subscribers and/or tracking company(s) are not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

13.2 If and when Zumbox sponsors promotions or sweepstakes, or third parties sponsor promotions or sweepstakes in conjunction with Zumbox, either Zumbox or the third party will post relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or registration area for the promotion or sweepstakes. That privacy information, to the extent it conflicts with this Privacy Policy, will govern that particular promotion or sweepstakes.

13.3 The third party websites may not have privacy policies, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you have any questions about how these other websites use your information, you should contact them directly.

**Facebook Connect**  
You can log in to our Site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web Site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Social Media Widgets**  
Our Web Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

14\. **California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your personally identifiable information to other parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com).

15\. **Employees, Access, Training and Expectations**

Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons and processes.

16\. **Merger, Sale or Change in Control**

In the event that Zumbox is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. We will notify you by email of a transfer of your personally identifiable information within 30 days from the time the transfer takes effect.

17\. **Changes**

In the future, we may make changes to this Privacy Policy, without prior notice. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy on the Site and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@zumbox.com](mailto:support@zumbox.com).
